<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyFitnessPal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_yoga_select">yoga_select</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="unit">Cm</string>
    <string name="femaletext">Female</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="startingheight">170</string>
    <string name="startingweight">55</string>
    <string name="startingage">22</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="calculate_your_bmi">Calculate Your BMI</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="boat_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Take a seat. Sit on your mat with your knees bent and your feet flat on the floor.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Lift and balance. Lean back, slightly rolling your lower back so that your tailbone tucks under without making direct contact with the ground.Use this leverage to lift your legs off the floor while your buttocks help maintain balance.You can also place your hands behind the outside of your knees to help stabilize your form.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Stretch and lengthen. While balancing on your sit bones, extend your legs out in front of you, slowly raising them into the air while you flatten your spine and lift your sternum towards the ceiling. Your body should form a V-shape at a 45-degree angle, with your sitting bones as the point of contact with the ground. Spread your shoulder blades wide and place your hands on the outside of your knees so your arms are parallel to the floor.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Hold and release. Keep your breathing steady and your gaze fixed on your big toes. Hold this pose for up to one minute.</string>
    <string name="bow_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Lie flat on your stomach. Keep your chin on the mat and your hands at your sides. Your hands should be palm up.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Exhale while you bend your knees. Bring your heels as close as you can to your buttocks. Your knees should be hip-width apart.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Lift your hands and take hold of your ankles. Be sure to grab the ankle and not the top part of the feet. Your fingers should wrap around the ankles, but your thumb does not. Keep your toes pointed.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Inhale and lift the heels away from the buttocks, keeping a hold of your ankles. Simultaneously, lift your head, chest, and thighs away from the mat. As you lift, rotate your shoulders safely and comfortably. At this point, only your core should touch the mat, while the rest of your body is lifted towards the ceiling.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Draw your tailbone into the mat to deepen the stretch. You should feel the stretch in your back as the weight and balance shifts to your core. Your chest and shoulders should feel open.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Look straight ahead and hold the pose for about 15 seconds while you focus on stretching, breathing, and balancing.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> Exhale and release the pose. Lower your head, chest, thighs, and feet back towards the mat. Let go of your ankles and return to your hands to your side. Relax for a few seconds and repeat the pose as needed or continue to your next pose.</string>
    <string name="cobra_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Place your palms flat on the ground directly under your shoulders. Bend your elbows straight back and hug them into your sides.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Pause for a moment looking straight down at your mat with your neck in a neutral position. Anchor your pubic bone to the floor.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Inhale to lift your chest off the floor. Roll your shoulders back and keep your low ribs on the floor. Make sure your elbows continue hugging your sides. Don\'t let them wing out to either side.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Keep your neck neutral. Don\’t crank it up. Your gaze should stay on the floor.</string>
    <string name="crescent_lunge"><b>Step 1.</b> From a low lunge, drop your back knee (the left knee, in this case) to the mat. If your knee is sensitive, you can place a blanket under your knee or double up your yoga mat for more cushioning.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Bring your hands onto your right knee and your right knee directly over your right ankle.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Inhale and raise your arms above your head, keeping the arms in line with your ears.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> To deepen into the lunge press firmly into your feet as you allow your hips to shift forward. As you do, your left thigh comes closer to the floor. To support engagement and to avoid sinking into the joints, hug your inner thighs in towards one another to create adduction.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> You may take the upper spine into a backbend if that feels comfortable.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Exhale to release the hands down, reframe the front foot, and release the pose.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> Repeat on the left side.</string>
    <string name="downward_facing_dog"><b>Step 1.</b> Come onto your hands and knees and bring your hands slightly in front of your shoulders. Spread your fingers wide, press down through your knuckles, and tuck your toes under.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Exhale as you lift your knees off the mat and reach your sit bones toward the ceiling. Keep your knees slightly bent as you lengthen your back.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Press the back of your thighs toward the wall behind you and stretch your heels toward the mat. Straighten your knees without locking them.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Press the base of your index fingers into the mat. Lift along your inner arms from your wrists to your shoulders. Firm your shoulder blades against your back, then widen them and draw them toward your tailbone. Relax your neck and keep your head between your upper arms.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Stay here for 10 or more breaths. As you exhale, bend your knees and lower yourself into Child’s Pose.</string>
    <string name="easy_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Arrange supportive padding (blanket, block, or bolster) under your sit bones so your hips will be higher than your knees when you come into the pose.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Come to sit on your padding in a comfortable, cross-legged position. Shift the flesh of your butt to each side with your hands so that your sit bones have a firm foundation.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Lean back and forth and side to side with your torso a few times to make sure your shoulders are aligned directly over your hips. Slide the shoulder blades down your back so your shoulders move away from your ears. The crown of your head should rise towards the ceiling.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Your hands can rest in your lap or on the tops of your thighs. Turn your palms up to be receptive or down to feel grounded.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> On your inhalations, feel your spine grow long. On your exhalations, root down through your seat.</string>
    <string name="half_pegion_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> From Downward Facing Dog, bring your right foot toward your right wrist, then set your knee and shin on the mat.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Straighten your left leg back — your legs will resemble the shape of the number 7. For most practitioners, aligning your shin parallel to the front edge of your mat is not accessible or necessary! Instead, work with your level of flexibility and place your heel a comfortable distance from your groin.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Align your right knee in line with your right hip.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Flex your right foot.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Walk your hands forward and lower your forehead to the mat.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Square your hips toward the mat.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> To release, walk your hands back and straighten your arms. Step back to Downward Facing Dog and switch sides.</string>
    <string name="low_lunge"><b>Step 1.</b> Start in Adho Mukha Svanasana / Downward Facing Dog.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> As you exhale, step your right foot forward, between your hands. Lower your left knee to the floor, sliding the foot back until you feel a nice stretch in the left hip and thigh.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Keep the hips low and level with each other.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> As you inhale, engage your lower belly and lift your chest away from the thigh, sweeping the arms up alongside your ears.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Look straight ahead or come into a gentle backbend with your gaze to your thumbs.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> As you exhale, lower your hands back down and step back to Downward Facing Dog.</string>
    <string name="upward_bow"><b>Step 1.</b> Lie on your back on the floor. Bend your knees and place your feet hip-width apart, a comfortable distance away from your hips. You want to be able to ground through your feet.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Place your hands flat on the mat either side of your head, fingers pointing towards the shoulders, elbows pointing up.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Press the shoulders down into the floor – feel how that opens and even lifts the chest somewhat. Press your inner feet down to keep your knees from falling out to the sides and to activate your glutes.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> On an inhalation, lift only the hips to the ceiling. Stay here for a breath or two.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Inhale and press into your hands to lift your body up. You can come either onto the crown of the head first (keeping the weight in your hands) or press up in one movement, straightening your arms as much as possible.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Once up in Wheel pose, think about length in the front body and an even arch in your back so you are not hinging in the lower back – you may scoop your tailbone forward slightly.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> To come out, exhale and look up to the ceiling as you lower yourself down to the floor, chin to your chest, taking care not to land directly on the top of your head. </string>
    <string name="warrior_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Stand up straight in Tadasana, or Mountain Pose. Take a deep breath and then exhale as you jump your feet far apart while spreading your arms out to the sides. Adjust your feet so that they are as far away from each other as possible. Check your heels to make sure they\'re in line with each other horizontally on the floor. Your toes should point straight ahead. Keep your arms straight and in line with your shoulders. Your palms should face down toward the floor.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Keeping your torso centered above your pelvis, rotate your right foot out 90 degrees to the right side. Rotate the toes of your left foot 45 degrees toward the right also. Balance your weight evenly between both feet and keep your left leg straight for the duration of this pose. You will know if you have completely straightened your left knee because when you do, the center of your left kneecap will be in line with the middle of your left ankle. Rotate both thighs outward and away from your pelvis.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Now take a breath and then breathe out as you bend your right knee down to a right angle. Bend down far enough so that your leg becomes parallel to the floor and level. Your shin should be perpendicular to the floor with your right knee directly above your right ankle. Press your left heel back firmly into the floor to balance as you bend the right knee.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Turn your head to the right and gaze at your right fingers. Keep your arms parallel to the floor and extend them to the sides, imagining that people are pulling your hands on each side of you in a tug of war. Lengthen both sides of your torso.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Hold this position for at least 30 seconds. Over time, you will be able to stay for up to a minute. Breathe in as you come out of the pose by straightening your right leg and then turning your feet back to face forward again. Now repeat the pose on the other side and hold it for the same amount of time.</string>
    <string name="warrior_pose_3"><b>Step 1.</b> Begin in Warrior I, which is a lunge with your right foot forward, knee bent 90 degrees with knee over the foot, and rear leg extended. Bring your hands to your hips.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Lean forward to bring your weight into your right (forward) foot. Keep your left (rear) knee bent as you float your left foot up away from the floor about a foot.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Straighten your right leg and continue to bring your torso toward a parallel position to the floor. Use your torso going forward to counterbalance your left leg lifting and extending straight back. Eventually, both the torso and the left leg will come parallel to the floor at roughly the same time. Keep the neck relaxed, as if it\'s the natural extension of the spine. Your gaze stays down towards the floor.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Fully extend the left (upper) leg. Keep both hips level and pointing toward the floor. The left hips tends to want to cock up so keep pointing it toward the floor. Your hands on your hips can help you feel this.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Flex the left (upper) foot and keep the toes pointing down at the floor. Actively engage the muscles of the left leg.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Bring your arms back along your sides when you are ready.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> Bend your right leg to step back to Warrior I.\n\n<b>Step 8.</b> Repeat the pose on the other side.</string>

    <string-array name="gender_array">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>