<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyFitnessPal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_yoga_select">yoga_select</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="unit">Cm</string>
    <string name="femaletext">Female</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="startingheight">170</string>
    <string name="startingweight">55</string>
    <string name="startingage">22</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="calculate_your_bmi">Calculate Your BMI</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="boat_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Take a seat. Sit on your mat with your knees bent and your feet flat on the floor.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Lift and balance. Lean back, slightly rolling your lower back so that your tailbone tucks under without making direct contact with the ground.Use this leverage to lift your legs off the floor while your buttocks help maintain balance.You can also place your hands behind the outside of your knees to help stabilize your form.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Stretch and lengthen. While balancing on your sit bones, extend your legs out in front of you, slowly raising them into the air while you flatten your spine and lift your sternum towards the ceiling. Your body should form a V-shape at a 45-degree angle, with your sitting bones as the point of contact with the ground. Spread your shoulder blades wide and place your hands on the outside of your knees so your arms are parallel to the floor.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Hold and release. Keep your breathing steady and your gaze fixed on your big toes. Hold this pose for up to one minute.</string>
    <string name="bow_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Lie flat on your stomach. Keep your chin on the mat and your hands at your sides. Your hands should be palm up.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Exhale while you bend your knees. Bring your heels as close as you can to your buttocks. Your knees should be hip-width apart.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Lift your hands and take hold of your ankles. Be sure to grab the ankle and not the top part of the feet. Your fingers should wrap around the ankles, but your thumb does not. Keep your toes pointed.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Inhale and lift the heels away from the buttocks, keeping a hold of your ankles. Simultaneously, lift your head, chest, and thighs away from the mat. As you lift, rotate your shoulders safely and comfortably. At this point, only your core should touch the mat, while the rest of your body is lifted towards the ceiling.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Draw your tailbone into the mat to deepen the stretch. You should feel the stretch in your back as the weight and balance shifts to your core. Your chest and shoulders should feel open.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Look straight ahead and hold the pose for about 15 seconds while you focus on stretching, breathing, and balancing.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> Exhale and release the pose. Lower your head, chest, thighs, and feet back towards the mat. Let go of your ankles and return to your hands to your side. Relax for a few seconds and repeat the pose as needed or continue to your next pose.</string>
    <string name="cobra_pose"><b>Step 1.</b> Place your palms flat on the ground directly under your shoulders. Bend your elbows straight back and hug them into your sides.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Pause for a moment looking straight down at your mat with your neck in a neutral position. Anchor your pubic bone to the floor.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Inhale to lift your chest off the floor. Roll your shoulders back and keep your low ribs on the floor. Make sure your elbows continue hugging your sides. Don't let them wing out to either side.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Keep your neck neutral. Don’t crank it up. Your gaze should stay on the floor.</string>
    <string name="crescent_lunge"><b>Step 1.</b> From a low lunge, drop your back knee (the left knee, in this case) to the mat. If your knee is sensitive, you can place a blanket under your knee or double up your yoga mat for more cushioning.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Bring your hands onto your right knee and your right knee directly over your right ankle.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Inhale and raise your arms above your head, keeping the arms in line with your ears.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> To deepen into the lunge press firmly into your feet as you allow your hips to shift forward. As you do, your left thigh comes closer to the floor. To support engagement and to avoid sinking into the joints, hug your inner thighs in towards one another to create adduction.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> You may take the upper spine into a backbend if that feels comfortable.\n\n<b>Step 6.</b> Exhale to release the hands down, reframe the front foot, and release the pose.\n\n<b>Step 7.</b> Repeat on the left side.</string>
    <string name="downward_facing_dog"><b>Step 1.</b> Come onto your hands and knees and bring your hands slightly in front of your shoulders. Spread your fingers wide, press down through your knuckles, and tuck your toes under.\n\n<b>Step 2.</b> Exhale as you lift your knees off the mat and reach your sit bones toward the ceiling. Keep your knees slightly bent as you lengthen your back.\n\n<b>Step 3.</b> Press the back of your thighs toward the wall behind you and stretch your heels toward the mat. Straighten your knees without locking them.\n\n<b>Step 4.</b> Press the base of your index fingers into the mat. Lift along your inner arms from your wrists to your shoulders. Firm your shoulder blades against your back, then widen them and draw them toward your tailbone. Relax your neck and keep your head between your upper arms.\n\n<b>Step 5.</b> Stay here for 10 or more breaths. As you exhale, bend your knees and lower yourself into Child’s Pose.</string>
</resources>